Hi there. My name is Arthur. I am the president and CEO of GC Events. We produce events nationally
all around the country, but mostly in LA and New York. We've been working with Apex Marketing and
Nathan for at least three years now. Prior to Nathan, we would hire other agencies to handle
our Google Ads, our meta ads, and we just found that they didn't feel substantial or thorough,
and their reports to us weren't really exactly sure of what was going on. After working with
Nathan, he helped to take our revenue from about 600k to about 1 million per year. So
it was definitely more than a 50% increase. He would check in with us and really report and let
us know about the numbers that were working behind the scenes, things like the impressions,
the conversions, all of the clicks, all the cost per conversions. We got a detailed understanding
of all of the numbers and how they fit in with our budget and what types of revenue they were
producing. I think Nathan and Apex Marketing, we've just really appreciated working with them.
They give you a sense that they genuinely care about your business doing better and not just giving
you a report at the end of the day, but actually understanding your business, doing things like
reporting the negatives and just making the campaign more optimized. And that was important to me.
I wanted to know that I could work with someone who actually is making progress along the way
and making this campaign better. Nathan and Apex highly recommended, honestly, again,
without them, we would have never crossed that $1 million in revenue mark. So thank you very much,
Nathan. Appreciate you.